#### **TEK RAJ PANT**

New Baneswor, Kathmandu | Mob: 9848810473 | tekrajpant224@gmail.com, https://github.com/tekraj

#### Summary

Web Developer specializing in front end as well as backend technologies. Involved in development of large scale dynamic web sites and web apps. Well versed in numerous programming language. Strong background in JavaScript and PHP.

# **Skill Highlights**

- HTML5,CSS3, Bootstrap
- JavaScript, jQuery, AngularJS, NodeJS
- Hybrid Mobile App Development With Ionic
- PHP Codelgniter and Laravel
- MySQL, MSSQL
- C#, ASP.NET MVC
- Familiar with Linux(Ubuntu)
- Familiar with git

# **Experience**

**Senior Software Engineer** 

June 2017-current

Orgware Construct Pvt. Ltd – Ekantkuna, Lalitpur

planetfundraiser.com support and maintains with Laravel

## Web Developer

Oct 2016-current

Muncha.com (Muncha Internet Ventures) – Ekantkuna, Lalitpur

- muncha.com new shopping portal website design, site architecture, front-end development, backend development using ASP.NET MVC(C#) and AngularJS with bootstrap
- iad.com.np advertisement platform with Revive adserver, Laravel
- Development of news portals (sajhasabal.com, bizpati.com etc.) using
  Codelgniter

Web Developer Jun 2015-Oct 2016

Surya Web Solutions Pvt. Ltd. – Sanepa, Lalitpur

Design and Development of Angel Investment Network site
 (<a href="https://www.angelinvestmentnetwork.co.uk/">https://www.angelinvestmentnetwork.co.uk/</a>) with FuelPHP and its mobile Application using Ionic framework

 Design and Development of ordamel shopping portal (<a href="http://de.ordamel.com/">http://de.ordamel.com/</a>) in FuelPHP along with its mobile application using lonic framework

## Web Designer/JavaScript Developer

July 2014-May 2015

Neolinx Pvt. Ltd. – Jawlakhel, Lalitpur

- UI design of suedtirol (<a href="http://www.suedtirol.com/">http://www.suedtirol.com/</a>) with jQuery, Bootstrap, CSS3
- Some small websites with WordPress (like http://qcbookshop.com/)

# **Developed some projects independently**

- Kathmandu University Exam Management System (Using CI)
- Bivuti.com (<a href="http://bivuti.com/">http://bivuti.com/</a>) using ASP.NET single page Application with AngularJS
- Pasalshop.com (https://pasalshop.com/) with Laravel
- Some other demo projects (custom PHP MVC framework - <a href="https://github.com/tekraj/electronics">https://github.com/tekraj/electronics</a> ), ecommerce site using MEAN stack Technology (https://github.com/tekraj/mean-app)

## **Educational Qualification**

- Pursuing M.Sc. CS(4<sup>th</sup> sem) NCIT College Balkumari Lalitpur 2016current
- B.Sc. Physics From Siddanath Science Campus Mahendranagar 2009-2012
- 12th from Siddanath Science Campus Mahendranagar 2006-2008
- 10th from Baijnath Higher Secondary School Mahendranagar Kanchanpur 2006

## **Trainings**

- 3 months Training in C/C++ from **Ducat Institute** Noida UP India 2013
- 6 Months Training in Web Designing/UI Designing From Tech Altum Noida UP India – 2013/2014
- 2 months Training in Advance PHP From Broadway Infosys Nepal-2015